{
  "LevelId": 55,
  "Questions": [
    {
      "id": 555,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "AIRSPACES",
      "question": "the purpose of managing air traffic and ensuring safe and efficient flight operations"
    },
    {
      "id": 556,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "ADULTHOOD",
      "question": "life is characterized by maturity, independence, and typically begins around the age of 18"
    },
    {
      "id": 557,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "MIGRAINES",
      "question": "recurring and intense headaches often accompanied by nausea,"
    },
    {
      "id": 558,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "COLOURFUL",
      "question": "visual quality characterized by a vibrant and varied display of hues, shades,"
    },
    {
      "id": 559,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "DRIZZLING",
      "question": "weather phenomenon is characterized by light rain falling in fine, mist-like droplets,"
    },
    {
      "id": 560,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "DIAMONDED",
      "question": "describe an object or surface adorned or covered with diamonds,"
    },
    {
      "id": 561,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "BEACHWEAR",
      "question": "describe clothing, typically casual and lightweight, designed for wear at the beach"
    },
    {
      "id": 562,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "MUDSTONES",
      "question": "sedimentary rocks composed primarily of fine-grained mud or clay particles,"
    },
    {
      "id": 563,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "BOOKRACKS",
      "question": "item is designed for holding and organizing books, typically with horizontal shelves,"
    },
    {
      "id": 564,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "BARABICELS",
      "question": "bristle-like structures found on certain plants, often serving a protective or sensory function,"
    },
    {
      "id": 565,
      "level_image": 0,
      "answer_text": "CONFIDENCE",
      "question": "state of self-assurance, belief in one's abilities, and a positive outlook"
    }
  ]
}